DANIEL RICCIARDO

SKILLS

Language

Javascript · Typescript · C++ · C# · PHP · Python · Java · HTML · CSS

Frameworks

React · Vue · Angular JS · Angular 2+ · React Native · Laravel · Flutter ·

 ${\sf Django} \cdot {\sf Next.js} \cdot {\sf Express.js} \cdot {\sf Nuxt.js}$

Libraries/APIs

 $\mathsf{D3.js} \cdot \mathsf{jQuery} \cdot \mathsf{WebRTC} \cdot \mathsf{Socket.IO}$

Tools

AWS · Git · Github · Jira · Trello ·

Mocha · Webpack · Babel

Platforms

MacOS · Docker · AWS Lambda ·

Windows

Storage

MySQL · MongoDB · AWS S3 ·

Amazon DynamoDB

LANGUAGES

Polish Native

English Proficient

Senior Full Stack Developer

RESUME PROFILE

I'm a passionate, enthusiastic, and professional Full-Stack Developer who loves nothing more than creating and developing many kinds of web and mobile apps using all the skills I've acquired over 6 years of dedication to studying and developing. My goal with all my clients is to listen, learn, understand, and execute to the highest level. I always aim to deliver what the client requires, but if I feel there's a better solution, I'm always willing to give them some input and direction if wanted. A happy client is a successful project to me

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

06/2016 - 11/2017

FIVELY Warsaw, Poland

- Created reusable D3.js charts using Raphael.js to draw SVG on browsers.
- · Handled responsive design layouts for views.
- Implemented reusable components for UX using jQuery.
- Created an xQuery Selector generator from an HTML Element DOMNode.
- · Created a Pop CSS editor for elements.

Web Developer

11/2017 - 07/2019

THE SOFTWARE HOUSE

Gliwice, Poland

- Created a new front-end app based on React and Redux.
- Added a Hot module replacement plugin to Webpack.
- Worked with legacy code on the server side, able to understand the principles behind it and make it work again.

Full Stack Developer

08/2019 - 12/2019

STEELKIWI

California, US

- Developed a single-page application that is used as a management tool for law entities; used React and Apollo.
- Created AWS Lambda functions to track and store the details of law entities.
- Updated the back end and GraphQL.

Senior Full Stack Developer

01/2020 - 03/2022

CodeEpsilonSTX NEXT

Poznan, Poland

- · Worked on providing API endpoints with Node.js/Inversify and MongoDB.
- Built from scratch admin platform for managing platform's database entities and users using React, Node.js, and Mongoose.
- Implemented complex UI components with React/TypeScript and SCSS.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering 2006 - 2010

Warsaw University of Technology

Bachelor of Computer Science

University of Lodz

2012 - 2015

